Donald Law

Watkinsville, Georgia 30677 | + 770 687 8692 | donald.mclarenlaw @gmail.com

Career Summary

Recent Management Information Systems graduate from the University of Georgia with practical experience in software development, data analysis, and IT service support. As a freelance Lua Developer, I played a key role in developing an independent entertainment project that became a flagship product on its platform.

Education

Bachelor of Business Administration in Management Information Systems

University of Georgia - Terry College of Business (May 2024) - Dean's List, Zell Miller Scholar **Leadership Experience:** Life Scout BSA, UGA WUOG Officer, UGA E-Sports Officer; Student Supervisor **Volunteering:** Books for Keeps, Project Safe, Food Bank, Help Desk Worker

Programming Languages: Lua, Java, SQL, Python, Apex; experienced in HTML5, CSS, and creating GUIs **Professional Tools:**

• Salesforce, Tableau, Microsoft Office Suite, Microsoft Excel, Jira, PowerBl, MySQL, Eclipse

Technical Skills:

- Advanced Excel (VLOOKUP, PivotTables, 250K+ rows); heavy SQL experience
- Experience analyzing and modeling complex data with Tableau, PowerBI, Visio, and JMP
- Working under Agile, Scrum, & Lean Six Sigma methodologies within the SDLC
- Exposure to AWS, Azure, Apache Tomcat, Docker, Kubernetes, and other backend tools
- Basic webpage creation & deployment through AWS EC2 and Elastic Beanstalk
- Creative tools including AutoCAD, Blender, Sony Vegas, Photoshop, Adobe Suite, & Unity

Work Experience

Service Technician & Data Analyst - Freelance

2020 - Present

• Data analytics & service-level technician work, Duties include advanced excel, consulting clients, running cable, PC assembly, home network setup, software debugging, etc.

Student Supervisor - Panda Express

Feb 2022 - Sept 2023

- Lead and mentored a team of 8+ students in a fast paced, high-volume environment.
- Trained new hires; developed excellent communication & time management skills

Project Experience

Junior Lua Developer & Data Analyst - Private Contract

Feb 2018 - Oct 2021

- Vital in the development of a Lua-based game dev application, created 3D models and scripted assets for a product that has generated 500k+ USD in revenue.
- Produced dashboards in Excel to analyze in-game purchase data, directly increasing profits
- Worked with technologies including Lua, Jira, Excel, Blender, AutoCAD, and Photoshop

Systems Analysis and Design Capstone Project

May 2024

- Lead the development of a Tenant Rental Application in Salesforce using Apex.
- Automated key functions including maintenance requests, tenant swaps, and payments.